

DANIEL BABILONIA

Web Developer

About Me

I am a passionate web developer with expertise in both front-end and back-end development. As a freelance developer, I have worked on diverse projects and I am always eager to learn new technologies. I possess excellent soft skills, developed through my previous work in customer service, allowing me to effectively communicate and deliver solutions that exceed expectations.

Experience

2023 - Act. **Technical Support Specialist**

Kodland

As a part-time Technical Support Specialist, I diagnosed and resolved software and hardware issues, configured systems, documented customer inquiries, and provided timely feedback. My problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and ability to work independently and as part of a team contributed to my success in this role.

2022 - Act. Frontend Developer

Freelance

Creating responsive projects and layout of web pages using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Bootstrap, Bootswatch and Redux and implementing backend structures with Node Js

Bilingual Customer Service Representative 2021 - 2023

Teleperformance

For over a year, I worked as a Bilingual Customer Service Representative in the Payments LOB of eBay, where I acquired customer service skills in a bilingual environment and was able to develop my problem-solving and teamwork abilities.

Frontend Developer 2020 - 2021

Lovelace Dev

I worked as a Frontend Developer at Lovelace, using React.is and Node.is. My responsibilities included creating and designing the user interface, making sure the application was functional and easy to use. I implemented user components, responsive layouts and managed user permissions, optimizing the user experience.

Contact Me

(+57) 301 405 6354 Medellin - Antioquia (Open to

dantealigheri.1998@gmail.com Additional Information:

Portfolio Web

https://danielbabilonia.netlify.app/

Education

Computer Systems and Engineering

Full Stack Web Developer

Lenguages

English







Spanish







Programming Skills

JavaScript















PSQL



Node IS

References

Mauricio Maldonado Iturriago

mauriciomaldo.14@gmail.com Phone number:

Mauricio Andrés Pacheco Perez

Phone number: +57 315 668 4893



DANIEL BABILONIA

Desarrollador Web

Sobre Mi

Soy un desarrollador web apasionado y con experiencia, con habilidades en el desarrollo tanto en el front-end como en el back-end. Como desarrollador independiente, he trabajado en diversos proyectos y siempre estoy ansioso por aprender nuevas tecnologías. Poseo excelentes habilidades sociales, desarrolladas a través de mi experiencia previa en servicio al cliente, lo que me permite comunicarme efectivamente y brindar soluciones que superan las expectativas.

Experiencia

2023 - Act. Technical Support Specialist

haelbox

Como Especialista en Soporte Técnico, diagnosticaba y resolvía problemas de software y hardware, configuraba sistemas, documentaba consultas de clientes y proporcionaba comentarios oportunos. Mis habilidades para resolver problemas, atención al detalle y capacidad para trabajar de manera independiente y en equipo contribuyeron a mi éxito en este rol.

2021 - Act. Desarrollo Frontend

Freelance

Creación de proyectos responsive y maquetación de sitios web con JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Bootstrap, Bootswatch y Redux así como implementación de estructuras backend con Node Js y PSQL.

2021 - 2023 Representante de Servicio al Cliente Bilingüe.

Teleperformance

Durante más de un año trabajé como Representante de Servicio al Cliente Bilingüe en el LOB de Payments de eBay, donde adquirí habilidades en atención al cliente en un ambiente bilingüe y pude desarrollar mi capacidad de solución de problemas y trabajo en equipo.

2020 - 2021 Desarrollador Frontend

Lovelace Dev

Trabajé como desarrollador Frontend en Lovelace, utilizando React.js y Node.js. Mis responsabilidades incluyeron la creactor y diseño de la interfaz de usuario, asegurándome de que la aplicación fuera funcional y fácil de usar. Implementé componentes de usuario, diseños responsivos y gestioné los permisos de usuario, optimizando la experiencia de usuario.

Contacto

(+57) 301 405 6354 Medellin - Antioquia (Abierto a cambios) dantealigheri.1998@qmail.com

danteangneri.1770@ginan.

Additional Information:

Portfolio Web

https://danielbabilonia.netlify.app/

Educación

Ingenieria de Sistemas y Computacion

Universidad del Nort 2016 - 2019

Desarollador Web FullStack

Escuela de Ciencias de Computacion Academlo 2022 - 2023

Idiomas

Inglés



Habilidades Nativo





CSS

React JS

PSQL

Node JS

Referencias

Mauricio Maldonado Iturriago

Cofundador de Lovelace

Email:

mauriciomaldo.14@gmail.com Número Telefónico: +57 302 424 1105

Mauricio Andrés Pacheco Perez

Electronical Engineer and Mobile Developer

Email:

mauriciopachper1998@gmail.com Número Telefónico: +57 315 668 4893